Guide to the C-SPAN records, 1809, 1978-2012
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center
- Series 4: Press Releases (Boxes 61-75), 1985-2002
  - Congressional Dinner Roast at the Washington Press Club, January 23, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 24)
  - American Profiles Features Louis Rukeyser and Nina Totenberg, January 24, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 25)
  - Election '92 New Hampshire Programming, January 24, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 26)
  - Road to the White House Features Behind the Scenes Presidential Campaign Trail, January 24, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 27)
  - Beating Bush; A Panel Discussion with the Experts, January 28, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 28)
  - First Year in Congress with Four Freshmen, January 28, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 29)
  - America and the courts Features Alfred Goodwin Speech, January 29, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 30)
  - National Governors' Association Meeting, January 29, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 31)
  - Road to the White House Features New Hampshire, January 29, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 32)
  - Richard Nixon Interview Press Release and Transcript, February 1992 (Box 70, Folder 33)
  - C-SPAN Statement Regarding S.12, February 3, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 34)
  - Iowa Caucus Coverage, February 6, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 35)
  - Election '92 Coverage, February 7, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 36)
  - New Hampshire Primary Coverage, February 10, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 37)
  - Road to the White House Live From New Hampshire, February 12, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 38)
  - Road to the White House Discusses New Hampshire and South Dakota Primary, February 19, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 39)
  - Road to the White House Features Vintage Campaign Advertisements, February 20, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 40)
  - Year End C-SPAN Statistics, February 21, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Election '92 High School Forum, February 26, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Road to the White House in Georgia and Maryland, February 26, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Super Tuesday Primary Coverage, February 27, March 9, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - America and the Courts Examiner Lucas v. South Carolina Coastal Council, March 5, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Illinois Senate Races, March 6, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Road to the White House Features Bob Kenrey, March 6, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Super Tuesday Primary Preview Programming, March 6, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Viewer Call-in Programs on World Affairs, March 11, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Road to the White House Looks at Primaries in the Great Lakes Region, March 12, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - America and the Courts Focuses on Separation of War Powers Between the President and Congress, March 13, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - National Press Club Speeches, March 13, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Beth Glatt Biography, March 16, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Illinois and Michigan Primary Coverage, March 16, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - National Press Club Speeches, March 19, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Road to the White House Features Withdrawal of Paul Tsongas, March 19, 1996 (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Cablevision's Educator Award Winners, March 20, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Television and Videocassette Recorder Equipment Awards to Schools, March 23, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Road to the White House Features Presidential and Senatorial Debates, March 27, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Election '92 Programming Schedule, March 30, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - General C-SPAN II Launch Press Release, April 1, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Road to the White House Features New York and Wisconsin Primaries, April 1, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 22)
  - British General Election Coverage, April 2, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - America and the Courts Program Focuses on Utah Abortion Case, April 3, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 24)
  - New York Primary Special Programming, April 3, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 25)
  - BBC Election Night Results Simulcast, April 8, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - Road to the White House Programming, April 9, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 27)
  - American Profiles Features Prominent Black Americans, April 14, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 28)
  - American Profiles Features Washington Based Entrepreneurs Bob Johnson and James Rouse, April 14, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - Road to the White House Features Jerry Brown, April 15, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 30)
  - American Profiles Features Sam Nunn and Colin Powell, April 16, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 31)
  - Oregon Senate Primary Debate, April 16, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 32)
  - America and the Courts Series on Pennsylvania Abortion Case, April 20, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 33)
  - Pennsylvania Presidential and Congressional Primaries Coverage, April 20, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 34)
  - C-SPAN and UNCF Award Elena L. Fernandez Scholarship, April 28, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 35)
  - Soviet Union News 1 Evening Newscast, April 28, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 36)
  - Road to the White House Features Bill Clinton, April 29, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 37)
  - Los Angeles and Civil Rights Special Programming, May 1, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 38)
  - C-SPAN Inaugural Ball Contest, May 4, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 39)
  - Viewer Call-in Program with Jerry Brown, May 4, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 40)
  - Opening of British Parliament, May 5, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 41)
  - Road to the White House Previews Democratic Convention, May 6, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 42)
  - Preview of West Virginia and California House and Senate Races, May 8, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 43)
  - Road to the White House Focus on Ross Perot, May 14, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 44)
  - Vietname Revisited Special, May 15, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 45)
  - Road to the White House Programming, May 20, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 46)
  - Brian Lamb National Radio Interview Transcript, May 26, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 47)
  - Garney Gary Field Technician, May 29, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 48)
  - Primary Night Programming, June 1, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 49)
  - Road to the White House Features California Primaries, June 1, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 50)
  - Road to the White House Looks at Bill Clinton and Ross Perot, June 3, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 51)
  - Presidential Press Conference, June 4, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 52)
  - America and the Courts Features John Paul Stevens, June 6, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 53)
  - Coverage of National Party Conventions, June 8, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 54)
  - Road to the White House Features Bill Clinton Town Hall, June 10, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - C-SPAN's Weekly Radio Journal on WAMU, June 12, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Bush-Yeltsin Summit, June 15, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Road to the White House Focues on Campaigns and Elections, June 17, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Spanish Translation of Democratic National Convention, June 18, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - America and the Courts Focus on Clarence Thomas, June 19, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Road to the White House Features Ross Perot, June 24, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Road to the White House Feature on Electoral College System, July 1, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Road to the White House Features Democratic National Convention, July 8, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Democratic National Convention Schedule, July 9, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Road to the White House Features Bill Clinton and Al Gore Rally, July 15, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - America and the Courts Assessment of the Supreme Court Term, July 17, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - National Governors' Association Conference, July 20, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Interview with Bill Clinton and Al Gore, July 22, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Al Gore Interview Transcript, July 23, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Bill Clinton Interview Transcript, July 23, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - Road to the White House Interview with Jimmy Carter, July 30, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - Coverage of Colorado State Races, August 3, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - USA Today Editorial Meeting with George Bush, August 3, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - Road to the White House Features Dan Quayle, August 5, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 20)
  - Road to the White House Programs, August 5-November 2, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - Road to the White House Interview with Barbara Bush, August 7, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 22)
  - Republican National Convention Coverage, August 11, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 23)
  - Republican National Convention Archival Footage, August 12, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 24)
  - Road to the White House Features George Bush and Dan Quayle, August 19, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 25)
  - High School Forums Discuss Presidential Debates, August 21, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 26)
  - Road to the White House Features Vice Presidential Candidates, September 3, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 27)
  - Town Meeting with Bill Clinton, September 8, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 28)
  - America and the Courts Airs Anthony Kennedy Speech, September 18, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 29)
  - Dan Quayle and Bill Clinton Campaign Events, September 18, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 30)
  - Senate Select Committee on POW/MIA Affairs, September 22, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 31)
  - Pennsylvania Senate Race Citizens Jury Program, September 24, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 32)
  - Road to the White House Features George Bush, September 25, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 33)
  - Ross Perot Re-entry into the Presidential Race, September 25, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 34)
  - Road to the White House Features Al Gore, September 30, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 35)
  - Representative From Three Presidential Tickets, October 2, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 36)
  - Presidential and Vice Presidential Debates, October 6, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 37)
  - American Profiles with William Weld and Robert Casey, October 8, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 38)
  - America and the Courts Looks at 1992-1992 Supreme Court, October 9, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 39)
  - Sunday Morning Show Roundtable with Bob Schieffer, Sam Donaldson, and Tim Russert, October 9, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 40)
  - Election '92 High School Forum in Michigan, October 13, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 41)
  - Election '92 High School Forum Series in Virginia, October 13, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 42)
  - Road to the White House Highlights Second Presidential Debate, October 14, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 43)
  - National Press Club Speech by Charles Rangel, October 21, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 44)
  - Road to the White House Programming, October 21, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 45)
  - America and the Courts Looks at Supreme Court Session, October 23, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 46)
  - C-SPAN New Promotions, October 23, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 47)
  - America and the Courts Look at Cameras in the Federal Courts, October 26, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 48)
  - Election Right Coverage, October 27, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 49)
  - Third Party Candidate Forum, October 29, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 50)
  - Key Moments From the Campaign Trail, October 29, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 51)
  - Short Subject Series Highlights International Parliaments, November 4, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 52)
  - C-SPAN Joins Turner Suit Against Cable Act, November 6, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 53)
  - Road to the White House Focus on New Administration, November 6, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 54)
  - New Faces of Washington Coverage, November 7, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 55)
  - Tip O'Neil Interview, November 11, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 56)
  - America and the Courts Upcoming Programs, November 13, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 57)
  - Newsweek Election Coverage Roundtable, November 13, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 58)
  - Short Subject Series Schedule, November 13, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 59)
  - Georgia State Senate Race, November 19, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 60)
  - Weekender Program Schedule, November 19, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Road to the White House Looks at Presidential Transition, November 20, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Bob Thomson Speech, November 21, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Customer Service Representative Election '92 Contest, November 23, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Mitch McConnell and George Mitchell Interviews on American Profiles, November 23, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - New Faces of Washington Program, November 23, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - America and the Courts Features Former Attorneys Generals, November 25, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Road to the White House Discussion on Presidential Transition, November 25, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - New C-SPAN Affiliates, December 3, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - C-SPAN Employee Programming Promotions, December 3, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - City Club of Cleveland Forum with Russell Means, December 9, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Road to the White House Preview of Little Rock Economic Conference, December 9, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Weekender Program Schedule, December 9, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Road to the White House Looks at New Cabinet Appointments, December 18, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - American Profiles Interviews John Murtha and Bill Thomas, December 21, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Viewer Call-in Show with Richard Lugar, December 22, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Road to the White House Interview of Marlin Fitzwater and Transcript, December 24, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Presidential Inauguration Programming, December 29, 1992-January 17, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - New Members of Congress Special, December 30, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - Approved Copy for Regularly Scheduled Programs, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - Bill Clinton Cabinet Confirmation Hearings, January 5-12, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - C-SPAN Awareness and Use Survey, January 6, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - Rhodes Scholars: The Oxford-American Connection, January 8, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 23)
  - Viewer Call-in with Bob Dole, January 21, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 24)
  - Republican National Committee Winter Meeting, January 27, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 25)
  - National Governors' Association Winter Meeting, January 29, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 26)
  - Bill Clinton Town Meeting, February 5, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 27)
  - Viewer Call-in With Mila Akmadzic, February 11, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 28)
  - Bill Clinton Address to Congress, February 16, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 29)
  - Booknotes Programming Schedule, February 17-March 10, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 30)
  - Live Viewer Call-in With Dick Armey, February 17, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 31)
  - Bill Clinton Economic Discussion, February 18, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 32)
  - Booknotes Interview with Kay Mills, February 20, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 33)
  - Viewer Call-in with Susan M. Phillips, February 22, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 34)
  - American Profile Interviews with Shirley Chisolm and Edward I. Perkins, February 25, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 35)
  - White House Special Program and Thomas "Mack" McCarty Transcript, March 2, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 36)
  - Attorney General Confirmation Hearings, March 4, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 37)
  - America and the Courts Look at Shaw, Pittman, Potts, and Towbridge Law Firm, March 10, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 38)
  - April Programming Schedule, March 12, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 39)
  - Continental Cablevision and C-SPAN2 Teleconference with Congressmen, March 15, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 40)
  - America and the Courts Program Schedule, March 15, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 41)
  - Upcoming Program Schedule, March 16, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 42)
  - Viewer Call-in Program with Internal Revenue Service Officers, March 17, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 43)
  - Booknotes Programming Schedule, March 22, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 44)
  - Evening News From Moscow, March 23, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 45)
  - French Parliamentary Election Returns, March 24, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 46)
  - Booknotes Programming Schedule, March 26, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 47)
  - President's Health Care Task Force, March 26, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 48)
  - May Programming Schedule, March 29, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 49)
  - C-SPAN Receives Peabody Award, April 1, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 50)
  - Forest Conference Coverage, April 1, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 51)
  - Bill Clinton and Boris Yeltsin Conference, April 2, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 52)
  - C-SPAN Networks Produce Nearly 7,000 Hours of Public Affairs Programming in 1992, April 7, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 53)
  - Coretta Scott King, April 7, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 54)
  - National Conference of Black Mayor Convention, April 7, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 55)
  - Live Viewer Call-in Program with Washington Couples, April 8, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 56)
  - Booknotes Programming Schedule, April 13, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 57)
  - National Gay and Lesbian March on Washington, April 19, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 58)
  - Viewer Call-in Program with Ben Bradlee and Sally Quinn Excerpts, April 19, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 59)
  - Health Care in America Series, April 20-28, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 60)
  - Russian Referendum Special Program, April 22-May 24, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 61)
  - African American Leadership National Press Club Speeches, April 26, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 62)
  - Judiciary Committee Hearing on Government Action in Waco, Texas, April 27, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 63)
  - Live Viewer Call-in with Barbara Boxer, May 10, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 64)
  - Texas Senate Candidates Debate, May 10, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 65)
  - Booknotes May Schedule, May 12, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 66)
  - Bill Clinton Town Meeting, May 13, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 67)
  - Base Closure and Realignment Commission Hearings, May 21-June 24, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 68)
  - American Profile Interviews with Richard Armey and Richard Gephardt, May 24, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 69)
  - Cable Act "Must Carry" Impact on C-SPAN, May 26, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 70)
  - Texas Senate Race, May 26, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Generic Release on Cable System Launching C-SPAN2, June-September 1993 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Booknotes June Schedule, June 2, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - DirecTV Includes C-SPAN, June 3, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Line Viewer Call-in with Leon Panetta, June 3, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Los Angeles Mayoral Race, June 4, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Road to the White House '96 Programming Begins, June 4, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - C-SPAN School Bus Brings Washington to Students, June 6, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Digital Cable Radio to Offer C-SPAN Audio Networks, June 6, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - C-SPAN and United Negro College Fund Award to Gelair Gibson, June 10, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Selection of New Canadian Prime Minister, June 11, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Jerry Lewis and Colin Peterson Discuss NAFTA, June 30, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Road to the White House '96 Program Schedule, June 30, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Bill Clinton Awards Philadelphia Liberty Medal to F.W. Deklerk and Nelson Mandela, July 1, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Booknotes July Schedule, July 1, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Newly-Elected Congressional Members Roundtable Discussion, July 1, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - New Members of C-SPAN Board of Directors, July 5-7, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - Democratic Leadership Council Survey of Ross Perot Supporters, July 6, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 18)
  - Bob Packwood Interview, July 8, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - Day-in-the-Life Series Features Susan Molinari, July 8, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 20)
  - Viewer Call-in Program with Al Gore, July 9, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 21)
  - Excerpts from Viewer Call-in Program with Bob Dole, July 13, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 22)
  - Ruth Bader Ginsburg Confirmation Hearings, July 14, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 23)
  - Bill Clinton Meeting with State Governors, July 16, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 24)
  - Interview with Robert Byrd, July 16, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 25)
  - Journalists' Roundtable, July 19, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 26)
  - Hillary Clinton on Health Care Reform, July 22, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 27)
  - Booknotes August Schedule, July 29, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 28)
  - Road to the White House '96 Looks at Carlos Moorhead California GOP Fundraiser, July 29, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 29)
  - Excerpts of Supreme Court Oral Arguments and Peter Irons Interview, August 3, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 30)
  - National Governors' Association and Interview with Ross Perot, August 10, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 31)
  - Pope John Paul II Visit with Bill Clinton, August 11, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 32)
  - Sunday Journal Launch, August 13, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 33)
  - 30th Anniverary March on Washington, August 19, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 34)
  - Bill Clinton Speech at Summer of Service Forum, August 30, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 35)
  - Labor Day Weekend Program Schedule, August 31, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 36)
  - Impact of 1968 on News and Public Policy Today, September 2, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 37)
  - Sunday Journal Interview with Warren Christopher, September 2, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 38)
  - Generic C-SPAN Channel Lauch Releases, September 7, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 39)
  - Interview with Betty Boothroyd, September 9, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 40)
  - Booknotes Program Schedule, September 10, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 41)
  - Sunday Programming Schedule, September 10, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 42)
  - White House Coverage of Middle East Peace Agreement, September 10, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 43)
  - C-SPAN School Bus Sneak Preview, September 14, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 44)
  - National Press Club Speaker Schedule, September 16, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 45)
  - Anti-North American Free Trade Rally, September 17, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 46)
  - Bill Clinton Speech on Health Care Reform, September 17, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 47)
  - Booknotes October Schedule, September 29, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 48)
  - Road to the White House '96 Looks at Lamar Alexander, October 5, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 49)
  - American Profiles Interviews with Len Downie and A.M. Rosenthal, October 6, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 50)
  - California Legislatures Hearings on School Vouchers, October 8, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 51)
  - Oval Office Interview with Bill Clinton, October 13, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 52)
  - C-SPAN School Bus, October 15, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 53)
  - New Jersey Gubernatorial Debate, October 20, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 54)
  - C-SPAN School Bus Launch, October 22, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 55)
  - Live Coverage of Canadian Elections, October 22, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 56)
  - America and the Courts Preview of Supreme Court Music Copyright and Case, October 26, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 57)
  - Viewer Call-in Program to Space Shuttle Columbia, October 26, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 58)
  - Bill Clinton Speech on John F. Kennedy, October 27, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 59)
  - C-SPAN High School Forum with Richard Riley, October 27, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 60)
  - Booknotes October and November Schedule, October 28, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 61)
  - Senate Ethic Committee's Attempt to Subpoena Robert Packwood Diaries, October 29, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 62)
  - C-SPAN School Bus Visits W. Bruce Evans, Jr. High, November 2, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 63)
  - C-SPAN School Bus Comes to Canton, Ohio, November 8, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 64)
  - Live Coverage of NAFTA Vote, November 15, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 65)
  - America and the Courts Speeches by Ruth Bader Ginsberg and Clarence Thomas, November 23, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 66)
  - American Profile Interviews with John Kasich and Kweisi Mfume, November 23, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 67)
  - C-SPAN School Bus in Anaheim, California, November 30, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 68)
  - Public Relations, Materials for Beacon Award for C-SPAN Bus, December 1993 (Box 74, Folder 69)
  - C-SPAN Signs Contract with America Online, December 1, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 70)
  - Booknotes Schedule in December and 5.25" Floppy Disk, December 3, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 71)
  - Live Telecasts of Five Overnight Space Walks by Space Shuttle Endeavor Crew, December 3, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 72)
  - Live Coverage of Senate Hearing on Cable Television Mega-Mergers, December 13, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 73)
  - A Day with Alan Simpson, December 25, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 74)
  - American Profiles Features David Bonior and David Dreier, December 20, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 75)
  - America and the Courts Looks at Cameras in Federal Courtrooms, December 21, 1993 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - C-SPAN/Scholastic/Close-up National Student Town Meeting, December 23, 1993 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Special Holiday Programming, December 23, 1993 (Box 75, Folder 3)